var TriviaQuestions = [
    // Question #1
    { theQuestion: "When did Pearl Jam release their album, 'Ten'?", 
        opt1: '1989',
        opt2: '1991',
        opt3: '1993',
        opt4: '1994',
        correct: '1991' },
    
    // Question #2
    { theQuestion: "What band did the drummer from Nirvana go on to form after the death of Kurt Cobain?",
        opt1: 'Foo Fighters',
        opt2: 'Mother Love Bone',
        opt3: 'Alice in Chains',
        opt4: 'Slayer',
        correct: 'Foo Fighters' },

    // Question #3
    { theQuestion: "What project formed as a response to the death of Andrew Wood, the lead singer of Mother Love Bone?",
        opt1: 'Mad Season',
        opt2: 'Pearl Jam',
        opt3: 'Green River',
        opt4: 'Temple of the Dog',
        correct: 'Temple of the Dog' },

    // Question #4
    { theQuestion: "What group did NOT include vocals by singer Chris Cornell?",
        opt1: 'Soundgarden',
        opt2: 'Audioslave',
        opt3: 'Temple of the Dog',
        opt4: 'Mad Season',
        correct: 'Mad Season' },

    // Question #5
    { theQuestion: "What vocalist, along with singer/guitarist Jerry Cantrell, created the eerie vocal harmonies for the band Alice in Chains?",
        opt1: 'Eddie Vedder',
        opt2: 'Chris Cornell',
        opt3: 'Layne Staley',
        opt4: 'Scott Weiland',
        correct: 'Layne Staley' },

    // Question #6
    { theQuestion: "Which grunge band featured a pair of brothers on guitar and bass?",
        opt1: 'Pearl Jam',
        opt2: 'Stone Temple Pilots',
        opt3: 'Black Flag',
        opt4: 'Silverchair',
        correct: 'Stone Temple Pilots' },
        
    // Question #7
    { theQuestion: "Which band had members appear as guests during the Nirvana: Unplugged performance?",
        opt1: 'Meat Puppets',
        opt2: 'Black Flag',
        opt3: 'The Melvins',
        opt4: 'Black Sabbath',
        correct: 'Meat Puppets' },     

    // Question #8
    { theQuestion: "What year did Soundgarden release their most successful album to date, 'Superunknown'?",
        opt1: '1991',
        opt2: '1997',
        opt3: '1993',
        opt4: '1994',
        correct: '1994' },   

    // Question #9
    { theQuestion: "Which group mocked the band Metallica for 'selling out' during their unplugged performance?",
        opt1: 'Alice in Chains',
        opt2: 'Nirvana',
        opt3: 'Stone Temple Pilots',
        opt4: 'Pearl Jam',
        correct: 'Alice in Chains' },

    // Question #10
    { theQuestion: "Which Alice in Chains album featured a three-legged dog on it's cover?",
        opt1: 'Dirt',
        opt2: 'Alice in Chains',
        opt3: 'Facelift',
        opt4: 'Jar of Flies',
        correct: 'Alice in Chains' },

    // Question #11
    { theQuestion: "Which Soundgarden music video featured disturbing images and grotesque face distortions?",
        opt1: 'Burden in my Hand',
        opt2: 'My Wave',
        opt3: 'Black Hole Sun',
        opt4: 'Rusty Cage',
        correct: 'Black Hole Sun' },

    // Question #12
    { theQuestion: "What singer joined the remaining members of Mother Love Bone to form the band Pearl Jam?",
        opt1: 'Chris Cornell',
        opt2: 'Scott Weiland',
        opt3: 'Andrew Wood',
        opt4: 'Eddie Vedder',
        correct: 'Eddie Vedder' },

    // Question #13
    { theQuestion: "What year did Nirvana singer and guitarist Kurt Cobain commit suicide?",
        opt1: '1995',
        opt2: '1994',
        opt3: '1991',
        opt4: '1998',
        correct: '1994' },

    // Question #14
    { theQuestion: "What year did Stone Temple Pilots release it's debut album, 'Core'?",
        opt1: '1990',
        opt2: '1989',
        opt3: '1992',
        opt4: '1994',
        correct: '1992' },

    // Question #15
    { theQuestion: "What year did Alice in Chains re-unite and release their Unplugged album?",
        opt1: '1996',
        opt2: '1994',
        opt3: '1999',
        opt4: '1992',
        correct: '1996' },

    // Question #16
    { theQuestion: "For which of these bands did Matt Cameron play drums?",
        opt1: 'Blind Melon',
        opt2: 'Soundgarden',
        opt3: 'Nirvana',
        opt4: 'Gin Blossoms',
        correct: 'Soundgarden' },

    // Question #17
    { theQuestion: "Which of these record labels were associated with Grunge music?",
        opt1: 'Sony',
        opt2: 'Sub Pop',
        opt3: 'Rhino',
        opt4: 'Arista',
        correct: 'Sub Pop' },

    // Question #18
    { theQuestion: "Which of these singers replaced Layne Staley in Alice in Chains following his death?",
        opt1: 'William DuVall',
        opt2: 'Phil Anselmo',
        opt3: 'Maynard James Keenan',
        opt4: 'Pat Lachman',
        correct: 'William DuVall' },

    // Question #19
    { theQuestion: "Which band did not originate from Seattle, Washington?",
        opt1: 'Nirvana',
        opt2: 'Soundgarden',
        opt3: 'Alice in Chains',
        opt4: 'Pearl Jam',
        correct: 'Nirvana' },  

    // Question #20
    { theQuestion: "Which of these classic grunge bands didn't appear on the 'Sub Pop 200' compilation?",
        opt1: 'Soundgarden',
        opt2: 'Mud Honey',
        opt3: 'Alice in Chains',
        opt4: 'Green River',
        correct: 'Alice in Chains' },  

    // Question #21
    { theQuestion: "Which of these was the first band to record for the Seattle indie label, Sub Pop?",
        opt1: 'Green River',
        opt2: 'Mother Love Bone',
        opt3: 'Pearl Jam',
        opt4: 'Malfunkshun',
        correct: 'Green River' },  

    // Question #22
    { theQuestion: "Which Stone Temple Pilots album was commonly referred to as '12 Gracious Melodies'?",
        opt1: 'Core',
        opt2: 'No. 4',
        opt3: 'Shangri-La Dee Da',
        opt4: 'Purple',
        correct: 'Purple' }, 

    // Question #23
    { theQuestion: "What year did Layne Staley die of a drug overdose?",
        opt1: '2002',
        opt2: '2000',
        opt3: '1996',
        opt4: '2006',
        correct: '2002' }, 

    // Question #24
    { theQuestion: "How many different drummers did Nirvana have over it's history?",
        opt1: '2',
        opt2: '5',
        opt3: '4',
        opt4: '6',
        correct: '5' }, 

    // Question #25
    { theQuestion: "Which band was originally going to be named 'Mookie Blaylock' after the former NBA player?",
        opt1: 'Mother Love Bone',
        opt2: 'Green River',
        opt3: 'Deftones',
        opt4: 'Pearl Jam',
        correct: 'Pearl Jam' }, 

    // Question #26
    { theQuestion: "Which of these bands was the first to form together in 1984?",
        opt1: 'Alice in Chains',
        opt2: 'Pearl Jam',
        opt3: 'Nirvana',
        opt4: 'Soundgarden',
        correct: 'Soundgarden' }, 

    // Question #27
    { theQuestion: "Which band was the first band to sign a contract with a major record label?",
        opt1: 'Soundgarden',
        opt2: 'Pearl Jam',
        opt3: 'Nirvana',
        opt4: 'Stone Temple Pilots',
        correct: 'Soundgarden' }, 

    // Question #28
    { theQuestion: "Which movie featured Seattle grunge bands including Soundgarden and Pearl Jam?",
        opt1: 'Sleepless in Seattle',
        opt2: 'Singles',
        opt3: 'This is Spinal Tap',
        opt4: 'Rockstar',
        correct: 'Singles' }, 

    // Question #29
    { theQuestion: "What band's hit song included the following lyric: 'Steal the rhythm while you can'?",
        opt1: 'Mud Honey',
        opt2: 'Pearl Jam',
        opt3: 'Soundgarden',
        opt4: 'Nirvana',
        correct: 'Soundgarden' }, 

    // Question #30
    { theQuestion: "What is the name of Nirvana's debut album?",
        opt1: 'Bleach',
        opt2: 'In Utero',
        opt3: 'Unplugged in NY',
        opt4: 'Nevermind',
        correct: 'Bleach' }, 
    
];